http://www.gapstedwines.com.au/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Section 1 - What kinds of personal information do we collect?
When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.
If you purchase a product from us online, your credit card details will be collected and processed by an external payment gateway such as PayPal or Shopify Payments. We do not see or store your credit card details.
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
Email marketing (if applicable): We may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates. You may have given us this information when you joined one of our Wine Clubs, asked to receive our newsletter, or purchased from us.
Section 2 - Consent
How do you get my consent?When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no. How do I withdraw my consent?If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at wineclub@gapstedwines.com.au or mailing us at:
Gapsted Wines 3897 Great Alpine Road Gapsted VIC 3737 Australia
Section 3 - Disclosure
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.
Section 4 - How We Store Your Personal Information
Our online store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.
Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.
We also use MailChimp - an email marketing platform - to store some of the personal data you provide to us. This includes your name, address and email address, and the products you purchase from us, which we use to create distribution lists and send marketing and Wine Club emails.Payments:If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Privacy Statement.
Section 5 - How We Use Your Personal Information
We may use your personal information for the following purposes:
To fulfill wine and/or event orders
To send you marketing materials, including emails (unless otherwise indicated)
Section 6 - Third-Party Services
In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
As an example, if you are located in Australia and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service. LinksWhen you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
Section 7 - Security
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
Section 8 - Cookies
Apart from the information you give us, we may also automatically collect information about you when you visit our websites, including through the use of cookies. Cookies are small data files that are downloaded onto your computer when you visit a particular website. Examples of information we may collect include:
technical information such as your computer’s IP address and your browser type; and
information about your visit such as the products you viewed or searched for, the length of your visit and the pages that you visited.
Cookies help us gather and store information about visitors to our websites. They help our websites remember what you chose on previous pages (to avoid having to re-enter information) and can help us to identify you as a unique visitor, tailor content based on past visitation and provide you with an optimised experience. Our cookies typically do not gather personally identifiable information.
If you prefer not to receive cookies you can adjust your Internet browser to refuse cookies or to warn you when cookies are being used. However, parts of our website will not function if cookies are turned off.
Section 9 - Age Of Consent
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of 18 in your state of residence.
Section 10 - Changes To This Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.
Questions and Contact Information
If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact us at wineclub@gapstedwines.com.au or by mail at:
Gapsted WinesC/- Privacy Compliance Officer 3897 Great Alpine Road Gapsted VIC 3737Australia
Not a Wine Club Member? Sign up for our Newsletter
Sign up to get the latest on sales, events, new releases and more …
Quick Links
Home
Wine Club
Our Wines
Cellar Door & Restaurant
Information
About Us
Export
Employment
Terms of Use
Purchase Policy
Privacy Policy
Social
Warning: Under the Liquor Control Reform Act 1998 (Vic) it is an offence: For a licensee to sell liquor to under 18s (Penalty exceeds $19,000); For a person to supply liquor to under 18s (Penalty exceeds $19,000); For a person under the age of 18 years to purchase, receive, possess or consume liquor (Penalty exceeds $800).
Enjoy Gapsted Wines' products responsibly. For more information about the responsible consumption of alcohol, please visit www.drinkwise.org.au.
General liquor licence No. 31953214; Wine and Beer Producer's Licence No. 32602638.
© 2020 Gapsted Wines.
Site by Ascet Digital
Ecommerce Software by Shopify
